

shakhnoza ismailova Miss.

Email: \$k->email

Phone: \$k->phone

Address: \$k->address

Timeline

shakhnoza ismailova applied about 6 months ago

Candidate Profile

Summary

Excellent leadership and management skills. Having a strong communication to eliminate the possibility of errors due to miscommunication. Extensive experience completing administrative tasks and maintain organized approach to procurement. Incorporate evaluation and analysis to identify beneficial investments.

Work Experience (about 7 years total)

01-04-2017 - 27-08-2020

International Procurement/ CEO at þÿ ITALIAN HOME BMT LLC (about 3 years)

bÿ" Developed and built relationships with key suppliers and measured suppl bÿcost, quality, and service level metrics; "Assisted in negotiations with ver bÿdirectly from the factory. "Attended meetings with Engineers and Project I bÿManagement "Conclusion of international equipment supply contracts in the

01-08-2016 - 01-04-2017

Decor designer at þÿ ITALIAN HOME BMT LLC (about 1 years)

bÿ" Designing interiors (building/ exterior area/private villas); " Developing bÿmodeling team; " Developing web site/ Company prequalification documents

01-08-2015 - 01-08-2016

þÿBusiness analyst in Project: INFORMATION SYSTEM OF PU þÿMANAGEMENT at þÿLLC Fido-Biznes (about 1 years)

þÿ" Practical knowledge of a wide range of technologies, including SAP, ARIS þÿteams during system implementation by answering questions related to the Creating USER GUIDE for the exact System; bÿ "Prepared and executed presentations in a professional and assertive mat bÿmembers and vendors about business goals; "Created reports and docume bÿsystem Fido DocFLOW "Provided detailed information to management, sa management regarding trends based on research;

Education

02-09-2008 - 25-05-2011

Profession- economist of industrial production (Bachelor) at Tashkent State University of Economist

02-09-2004 - 25-05-2006

languages at Profession- economist of industrial production (Bachelor)

What is your motivation to join us?

as I person who works on self-development, it will be a great opportunity to provide all my skills and knowledge at this University and the meantime to get experience from the experts who work here.

What is your vision for the position?

My vision is to work closely with academic staff as well as a student who gets knowledge here. It will help to understand the real needs of both professors and students, and this, in turn, will develop my capacity building to be efficient in my job.